# **Brayden Singleton**

Lee's Summit, MO 64086 (816)-875-5227 singletonbrayden@gmail.com

Confident Computer Technician with expertise in help desk environments, assisting both employees and customers with technical issues. Versatile IT Technician ready to fix faulty hardware, install new assets and support continuous business operations. Adapts to rapidly changing work situations and employee realities. Consistently beneficial to all technical operations and technological procedures.

## **Websites**

https://braydensingleton.github.io/project.html

## **Skills**

- CSS design (HTML)
- Proficient in Java, C++, Python, HTML, SQL
- Digital Forensics (Kali Linux)
- Adaptability and Flexibility
- Constructive Feedback
- Skill Development
- Seal of Biliteracy in Spanish

# **Work History**

#### Intern

LSCV CPA's, Lees Summit, MO

June 2022 - Current

 Responsible for providing technical support for IT systems, addressing and resolving hardware and software issues, and assisting with system maintenance. Additionally, provide assistance in the payroll department by processing payroll transactions, ensuring accurate employee compensation, and managing related administrative tasks.

### Intern

Trust Technology Solutions, Leawood, KS

June 2021 - August 2021

 Provided comprehensive helpdesk support to users, effectively addressing and resolving technical issues. Managed and completed trouble tickets in a timely manner, ensuring user concerns were addressed promptly and accurately.

#### Coach

Oak Tree Farms Swim Team, Lees Summit, MO

May 2020 - August 2020

Developed and implemented personalized training programs for young competitive swimmers, focusing
on enhancing their individual skills, strength, and endurance. These programs were tailored to address
specific needs and goals, while also incorporating strategies to improve overall team performance.

## **Education**

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science May 2024

University of Missouri-Kansas City, Kansas City, MO

Dean's List Fall 2022

3.509 GPA

Bachelor of Science May 2021

Manhattan Christian College, Manhattan, KS

Attended MCC on a soccer scholarship where I won our Conference and was named NCCAA All Region

## **Accomplishments**

- Seal of Biliteracy
- NCCAA All Region

# **Projects**

Created a website and database for Commerce Bank Personal Website

Personal Website

https://braydensingleton.github.io/project.html

### **CrossFit**

CrossFit is a high-intensity fitness training program that combines elements of weightlifting, cardio, and functional movements, to improve overall fitness through a mix of aerobic exercise, bodyweight exercises, and weightlifting.

## Languages

Spanish English